https://www.confetti.co.uk/information/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy by Guest Blogger / 23/05/2018Ocean Media Group is committed to protecting your privacy and takes its responsibilities regarding the security of user information very seriously. This privacy statement sets out how Ocean Media Group complies with both UK and European Union data protection requirements. We have structured our website so that you can visit without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us with any information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Statement.“Ocean Media Group” includes the brands Baby & Toddler Show, National Wedding Show, The Wedding Fairs, Confetti, Wedding Style Collective, Bridal Buyer, London Bridal Week, The Harrogate Bridal Show, The Stationery Show, Stationery Matters, The Flooring Show, Homes, Housing, Housing Expert, Inside Housing and Social Housing and their related events, products and services. If you wish to receive a list of our trading companies please send a request to dataprotect@oceanmedia.co.ukIf you have any queries about the policy or to be removed from Ocean Media Group’s database, please get in touch with us using dataprotect@oceanmedia.co.uk or write to us at Ocean Media Group, 3rd Floor, 4 Harbour Exchange Square, Isle of Dogs, London, E14 9GE and we will do our best to answer your questions.This privacy policy was last updated on 23rd May 2018What we collectPersonal data Under the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) personal data is defined as:“any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person”.The personal data we may collect from you and process is:Contact details, such as name, postal address, telephone number and email addressFinancial and transaction data, such as credit or debit card number, and bank account information where necessary for processing an orderDemographic information such as seniority, preferences and interestsOther Personal data such as gender, race, ethnicity and sexual orientationOther data that we may collect from you is:Browser and device data, such as IP address, device type, operating system and Internet browser typeTransaction data, such as purchases, purchase amount, date of purchase and payment methodCookie and tracking technology data, such as time spent on website, pages visited and other anonymous traffic dataHow we use your information This privacy notice tells you how we, Ocean Media Group, will collect and use your personal data for:To provide our products and servicesTo process your orderTo personalise the website for youTo contact you in response to a specific enquiryTo send you promotional emails and mailings about Ocean Media Group’s products, services, offers and other things that we think may be relevant to youTo contact you via telephone about Ocean Media Group’s products and services that we think may be relevant to youTo contact you via email or telephone for market research reasons.To improve or modify our servicesFor audits, regulatory purposes, and compliance with industry standardsTo conduct aggregate analysis and develop business intelligence that enables us to operate, protect, make informed decisions, and report on the performance of, our businessWhy does Ocean Media Group need to collect and store personal data? We may pass your personal data on to third-party service providers contracted to Ocean Media Group in the course of dealing with you. Any third parties that we may share your data with are obliged to keep your details securely, and to use them only to fulfil the service they provide you on our behalf. This includes but is not limited to, event registration, subscription fulfilment and email marketing. When they no longer need your data to fulfil this service, they will dispose of the details in line with Ocean Media Group’s procedures. If we wish to pass your sensitive personal data onto a third party we will only do so once we have obtained your consent, unless we are legally required to do otherwise.Click here if you would like to know who we share your data with and why.International transfers of dataIn some cases the personal data we collect from you might be processed outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), such as the United States, Canada and India. These countries may not have the same protections for your personal data as the EEA has. However, we are obliged to ensure that the personal data that is processed by us and our suppliers outside of the EEA is protected in the same ways as it would be if it was processed within the EEA. There are therefore certain safeguards in place when your data is processed outside of the EEA.How will Ocean Media Group use the personal data it collects about me? Ocean Media Group will process (collect, store and use) the information you provide in a manner compatible with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We will endeavour to keep your information accurate and up to date, and not keep it for longer than is necessary. Ocean Media Group is required to retain information in accordance with the law, such as information needed for income tax and audit purposes. How long certain kinds of personal data should be kept may also be governed by specific business-sector requirements and agreed practices. Personal data may be held in addition to these periods depending on individual business needs. Under what circumstances will Ocean Media Group contact me? Our aim is not to be intrusive, and we undertake not to ask irrelevant or unnecessary questions. Moreover, the information you provide will be subject to rigorous measures and procedures to minimise the risk of unauthorised access or disclosure.Can I find out the personal data that the organisation holds about me? Ocean Media Group at your request can confirm what information we hold about you and how it is processed. If Ocean Media Group does hold personal data about you, you can request the following information:Identity and the contact details of the person or organisation that has determined how and why to process your data. In some cases, this will be a representative in the EU.Contact details of the data protection officer, where applicable.The purpose of the processing as well as the legal basis for processing.If the processing is based on the legitimate interests of Ocean Media Group or a third party, information about those interests.The categories of personal data collected, stored and processed.Recipient(s) or categories of recipients that the data is/will be disclosed to.If we intend to transfer the personal data to a third country or international organisation, information about how we ensure this is done securely. The EU has approved sending personal data to some countries because they meet a minimum standard of data protection. In other cases, we will ensure there are specific measures in place to secure your information.How long the data will be stored.Details of your rights to correct, erase, restrict or object to such processing.Information about your right to withdraw consent at any time.How to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.Whether the provision of personal data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract, as well as whether you are obliged to provide the personal data and the possible consequences of failing to provide such data.The source of personal data if it wasn’t collected directly from you.Any details and information of automated decision making, such as profiling, and any meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and expected consequences of such processing.What forms of ID will I need to provide in order to access this? Ocean Media Group accepts the following forms of ID when information on your personal data is requested:Passport, driving licence, birth certificate or utility bill (from last 3 months)  Share Share on Twitter
Share on Facebook
Share on Pinterest
< Previous article Next article >
Popular right now
Lifestyle and RelationshipsJoke Names, Phonetic Puns & Prank NamesMarch, 2007
Gift Lists & GiftingHow to Ask For Money as a Wedding GiftSeptember, 2020
SpeechesThe Groom’s SpeechAugust, 2020
Lifestyle and RelationshipsAristocratic & Royal NamesJune, 2015
SpeechesWedding Speeches: Who Traditionally Says What?September, 2020
SpeechesSample Speeches for Brides to Have Their Say on the Big DayAugust, 2019
Décor & Styling50 Stunning DIY Wedding CentrepiecesFebruary, 2020
CeremoniesWedding Ceremony Hymns: Popular Picks Everyone Will KnowJune, 2018
Planning & AdviceThe Ultimate Wedding Planning ChecklistDecember, 2020
Ceremonies15 Alternative Unity Ceremony Ideas for Your WeddingNovember, 2020 You might like: Lifestyle and RelationshipsJoke Names, Phonetic Puns & Prank NamesMarch, 2007
Gift Lists & GiftingHow to Ask For Money as a Wedding GiftSeptember, 2020
SpeechesThe Groom’s SpeechAugust, 2020
Lifestyle and RelationshipsAristocratic & Royal NamesJune, 2015 Sign up to our newsletter
Email** First Name**Last Name**Engagement Date
Date Format: MM slash DD slash YYYY Wedding Date
Date Format: MM slash DD slash YYYY PostcodeBy clicking 'join now' you are opting in being emailed about Confetti news and productsConfetti would like to send you information about our products including: Wedding Style Collective, The National Wedding Show and The Wedding Fairs. If you would like to receive this information please tick your preferences belowContact Preferences
By emailNameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Find Wedding Ideas, Inspiration, Venues and Services
Search for:
Subscribe to our NetworkStay connected with our network and get all the best Wedding Planning, Inspiration and Competitions directly into your inbox.
Subscribe
